{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Aarav", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "9988776655"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rahul", "transferred", "money", "to", "ICICI", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
{"tokens": ["Neha", "transferred", "money", "to", "HDFC", "account", "1234567890"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ACCOUNT_NUMBER"]}
